Narrator: Common adverb collocations
Adverb + adjective or past participle
Narrator: 1
M: readily available
Narrator: 2
F: fully aware
Narrator: 3
M: bitterly cold
Narrator: 4
M: fiercely competitive
Narrator: 5
F: quietly confident
Narrator: 6
F: ridiculously easy
Narrator: 7
M: hugely enjoyable
Narrator: 8
F: prohibitively expensive
Narrator: 9
M: perfectly normal
Narrator: 10
M: painfully thin
Narrator: 11
F: blissfully unaware
Narrator: 12
F: deeply unhappy
Narrator: 13
M: legally required
Narrator: 14
F: badly damaged
Narrator: 15
M: actively involved
Narrator: 16
M: happily married
Narrator: 17
F: sadly mistaken
Narrator: 18
F: reasonably priced
Narrator: 19
M: highly recommended
Narrator: 20
F: firmly attached